[
    {
        "id":1,
        "question": "What is C++?",
        "one":"C++ is an object oriented programming language",
        "two":"C++ is a procedural programming language",
        "three":"C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
        "four":"C++ is a functional programming language",
        "answer":"C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
        "one":"Default constructor",
        "two":"Parameterized constructor",
        "three":"Copy constructor",
        "four":"Friend constructor",
        "answer":"Friend constructor"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question": "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
        "one":"Left-right",
        "two":"Right-left",
        "three":"Bottom-up",
        "four":"Top-down",
        "answer":"Bottom-up"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question": "  Who invented C++?",
        "one":"Dennis Ritchie",
        "two":"Ken Thompson",
        "three":"Brian Kernighan",
        "four":"Bjarne Stroustrup",
        "answer":"Bjarne Stroustrup"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question": " Which of the following is the correct syntax of including a user defined header files in C++? ",
        "one":"#include [userdefined]",
        "two":"#include “userdefined”",
        "three":"#include <userdefined.h>",
        "four":"#include <userdefined>",
        "answer":"#include “userdefined”"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question": "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
        "one":"/* comment */",
        "two":"// comment */",
        "three":"// comment",
        "four":"both // comment or /* comment */",
        "answer":"both // comment or /* comment */"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question": "Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++?",
        "one":"hg",
        "two":"cpp",
        "three":"h",
        "four":"hf",
        "answer":"h"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question": "Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
        "one":"VAR_1234",
        "two":"$var_name",
        "three":"7VARNAME",
        "four":"7var_name",
        "answer":"VAR_1234"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question": "Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
        "one":"double",
        "two":"float",
        "three":"int",
        "four":"bool",
        "answer":"bool"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
        "one":"Based on the number of bits in the system",
        "two":"2 or 4",
        "three":"4",
        "four":"2",
        "answer":"Based on the number of bits in the system"
    },
    {
        "id":11,
        "question":"What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
        "one":"Based on the number of bits in the system",
        "two":"2 or 4",
        "three":"4",
        "four":"2",
        "answer":"Based on the number of bits in the system"
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "question":"What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
        "one":"Based on the number of bits in the system",
        "two":"2 or 4",
        "three":"4",
        "four":"2",
        "answer":"Based on the number of bits in the system"
    },
    {
        "id":13,
        "question":"What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
        "one":"Based on the number of bits in the system",
        "two":"2 or 4",
        "three":"4",
        "four":"2",
        "answer":"Based on the number of bits in the system"
    }
]